没有妒忌的都给你
阿娜特莫呓
基本诺库尼
基本诺克的达西属尼摩多尼
亚斯玛子尼
阿塔达罗塔美key
OK e cup say Le na
Ye e o e o e o
就够就够就够
他的塔诺他没你赢
老的麻斯耶稣耶耶稣耶稣
孔弄岂用阿瓦人的旧复古西颓图的
you bless me i am tommer shena heber day sinner mine father land
mine of wonderbacadways to god
dark would not bitter fear
these gatesignata land palomina
destroya deer helicopter
he knows he knows he knows
his dignity spread over days
yet this yet this yet this
thy once connected how they wounded mother does land flows
every time i close my eyes i always think of you
may my nation in countrymen turn to the lord
twenty four hours day and night i always pray for you
mayday fear of rabbit welcome to few days land China
中国中国中国
我为你祝福为你祷告相世界宣告
耶稣耶稣耶稣
恳求你怜悯
医治这地为中国为中国祝福
中国中国中国
我为你祝福为你祷告让世界宣告
耶稣耶稣耶稣
恳求你怜悯医治这里为中国祝福